wildforwags.com 2010-12-27

# PRIVACY & DISCLAIMERS :: Wild for Wags

### PRIVACY & DISCLAIMERS

Time posted: 12:19 pm

**_This site is no way affiliated with Walgreens, Walgreens Pharmacy, Walgreens.com or any other partner company or subsidiary of Walgreens in any way. I am not compensated by them for any information on this site nor am I employed by them._**

**What information do we collect?** We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
• To send periodic emails

**What do we use your information for?** The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.wildforwags.com](http://www.wildforwags.com/)

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  
This policy was last modified on 3/17/10
